<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>homepage on Pixelbooth</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in homepage on Pixelbooth</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>fr-FR</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:56:08 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Merci pour votre demande!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:56:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Votre formulaire a été soumis avec succès&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/&#34; class=&#34;btn btn-secondary&#34;&gt;Retour à l&#39;accueil&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third_post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/galleries/third_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/galleries/third_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;En portugais, « MUDA » veut dire jeune pousse de caféier. Le mot fait également référence au verbe « Mudar » qui signifie changer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Avec Cafés MUDA, nous voulons contribuer à notre échelle au changement en cours dans le monde du café en proposant des cafés de saison pour vous assurer une fraîcheur aromatique au moment de la dégustation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notre mission consiste à rendre le café de spécialité plus accessible tout en ayant conscience des enjeux à l’échelle mondiale. Le café étant un des produits les plus échangés dans le monde, son prix est fixé à la bourse souvent au détriment des producteurs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Informations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/infos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:28:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/infos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Qu’est-ce que PixelBooth ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;PixelBooth est un photomaton moderne, ludique et personnalisable conçu pour capturer vos moments&#xA;précieux lors de tous vos événements : mariages, anniversaires, soirées d’entreprise, ou tout autre&#xA;rassemblement festif. Basé à &lt;strong&gt;Amiens&lt;/strong&gt; et actif dans toute la région &lt;strong&gt;Hauts-de-France&lt;/strong&gt;,&#xA;PixelBooth est l’allié idéal pour vos événements locaux.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Comment ça marche ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simple et intuitif: Deux touches suffisent pour lancer la prise de vue.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Personnalisation: Choisissez entre une photo unique ou un collage de quatre.&#xA;Ajoutez un fond personnalisé pour correspondre au thème de votre événement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sauvegarde éco-responsable** : Pas d&amp;rsquo;impression papier inutile !&#xA;Toutes les photos sont enregistrées directement sur un disque dur intégré et dans le cloud, pour un&#xA;accès sécurisé et durable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pourquoi choisir PixelBooth ?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second_post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/galleries/second_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:30:40 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/galleries/second_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prepare the Filter: Fold the paper filter into a cone shape and rinse it in the Hario dripper with water just off the boil (about 205°F) to eliminate paper flavor and to heat up the mug or carafe you are brewing into. Discard the rinse water.&#xA;Add Coffee: Grind 21 grams (about 3 tablespoons) of coffee to be about as fine as kosher salt. Add the coffee to your brewer.&#xA;Blooming: Saturate the grounds with water right off the boil (about 205°F). Use just enough water to cover the grounds. Let it bloom for 15 seconds. The coffee should raise up and bubble a bit.&#xA;Pour Water: Pour water in a slow, even spiral, adding water every 10 to 15 seconds for an even extraction. Pour over the dark spots and avoid the light ones. You can pour up to 110g, then after counting around a minute, pour up to 200g, and give it a light stir to get rid of any harshness, and let it flow a bit.&#xA;Finish Brewing: The brewing process should be completed within 2 to 4 minutes. Once the coffee has finished brewing, discard the grounds.&#xA;Enjoy: Your coffee is now ready to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First_post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/galleries/first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:19:38 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/galleries/first_post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you can keep your head when all about you&#xA;Are losing theirs and blaming it on you,&#xA;If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,&#xA;But make allowance for their doubting too;&#xA;If you can wait and not be tired by waiting,&#xA;Or being lied about, don&amp;rsquo;t deal in lies,&#xA;Or being hated, don&amp;rsquo;t give way to hating,&#xA;And yet don&amp;rsquo;t look too good, nor talk too wise:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
